(Leonard:)Why do I always have
to carry the heavy stuff?
(Sheldon:)Well, it's very simple.
(Sheldon:)In our ragtag band of scientists
with nothing to lose...
(Sheldon:)...I'm the smart one.
Wolowitz is the funny one.
(Sheldon:)Koothrappali is the lovable foreigner...
(Sheldon:)...who struggles to understand our ways
and fails.
(Sheldon:)That leaves you, by default,
as the muscle.
(Leonard:)One more floor
and I'd be the pulled muscle.
(Penny(who is inside the apartment):)Oh, it's about time. I'm starving.
(Leonard:)Uh, well,
we didn't actually get Chinese food.
(Penny:)-Why not?
-Don't panic. This is better.
(Penny:)Oh, no. You didn't trade the food
for magic beans, did you?
(Sheldon:)Of course not. And, technically,
magic beans would be food.
Eating them would be a waste,
since you could plant them...
...and have a giant beanstalk which
would provide roughage for a small city.
(Penny:)Yeah, sometimes I don't listen.
(Penny:)Sometimes I just watch your jaw
go up and down.
We were on our way to the restaurant.
(Leonard:)We saw Adam West, so we followed him.